Guide to the International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers, Local 66 Records WAG.010
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series IV: Shop Files, 1937-1979, 4
  - R. Hoe: [see 22/6], 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - R. Hoe: [see 22/6], 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - R. Hoe: [see 22/6], 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence - 1954 strike, 1955 "bad year for business," personnel director V. Regan supports union as "democratic organization;" (later became a State Mediator); 1957-1959 absenteeism and unrest; 1962 - problems with the anti-union supervisor; 1963-1964 - relations with other unions (IAM, OEU, and Pattern-Makers) averting a strike, includes membership meetings minutes; 1969-1970 bankruptcy proceedings for the company., 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - R. Hoe: Correspondence [see 22/22], 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - R. Hoe: Arbitration: 1958-1960 background of cases; job-shoppers., 1958-1964 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - R. Hoe: Arbitration: 1958-1960 background of cases; job-shoppers., 1958-1964 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - R. Hoe: Arbitration: 1958-1960 background of cases; job-shoppers., 1958-1964 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - R. Hoe: Arbitration: 1958-1960 background of cases; job-shoppers., 1958-1964 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - R. Hoe: Arbitration: 1958-1960 background of cases; job-shoppers., 1958-1964 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - R. Hoe: General data: company reports, personnel, Benefits, 1953-1967 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - R. Hoe: General data: company reports, personnel, Benefits, 1953-1967 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - R. Hoe: General data: company reports, personnel, Benefits, 1953-1967 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - R. Hoe: General data: company reports, personnel, Benefits, 1953-1967 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - R. Hoe: General data: company reports, personnel, Benefits, 1953-1967 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - R. Hoe: General data: company reports, personnel, Benefits, 1953-1967 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - R. Hoe: Rate changes, reclassifications, new employees, terminations, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - John A. Johnson and Sons: litigation following Field Engineers Strike (1950-1951) includes long fight to get company to pay the arbitrator's award. Background testimony by JLR is included in first and last folders. (See also 12/43), 1950-1957 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - John A. Johnson and Sons: [see 23/1], 1950-1957 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - John A. Johnson and Sons: [see 23/1], 1950-1957 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - John A. Johnson and Sons: [see 23/1], 1950-1957 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - John A. Johnson and Sons: [see 23/1], 1950-1957 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - John A. Johnson and Sons: [see 23/1], 1950-1957 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - John A. Johnson and Sons: [see 23/1], 1950-1957 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - John A. Johnson and Sons: [see 23/1], 1950-1957 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - John A. Johnson and Sons: [see 23/1], 1950-1957 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - John A. Johnson and Sons: [see 23/1], 1950-1957 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Lummus Co.: Contracts, 1944-1969 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Lummus Co.: Contracts, 1944-1969 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Lummus Co.: Contracts, 1944-1969 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Lummus Co.: Contracts, 1944-1969 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Lummus Co.: Contracts, 1944-1969 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Lummus Co.: Contracts, 1944-1969 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations: early notes show company's draft proposals; 1952 Outlook article; patent/non-disclosure clause (1958); "cosier" relations through mid-1960s; 1966 strike for fair share of Lummus' prosperity; 1969 membership meeting discusses contract., 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Lummus Co.: Negotiations [see 23/17], 1943-1969 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Lummus Co.: Labor-management conferences and notes (between negotiations): 1946 postwar grievances by veterans wanting "their fair share" for saving the world for Lummus; company moves to Bloomfield, NJ, 1942-1967 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Lummus Co.: [see 23/37], 1942-1967 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Lummus Co.: [see 23/37], 1942-1967 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Lummus Co.: [see 23/37], 1942-1967 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Lummus Co.: [see 23/37], 1942-1967 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Lummus Co.: [see 23/37], 1942-1967 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Lummus Co.: [see 23/37], 1942-1967 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Lummus Co.: [see 23/37], 1942-1967 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Lummus Co.: [see 23/37], 1942-1967 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Lummus Co.: [see 23/37], 1942-1967 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Lummus Co.: [see 23/37], 1942-1967 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Lummus Co.: [see 23/37], 1942-1967 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Lummus Co.: [see 23/37], 1942-1967 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Lummus Co.: Grievances: job-shopping (farming union work out to non-unionized engineers); Rotondi's discharge includes charge of homosexuality and mental instability (see also Membership File: Rotondi), 1950-1967 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Lummus Co.: Grievances [see 23/50], 1950-1967 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Lummus Co.: Grievances [see 23/50], 1950-1967 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Lummus Co.: Grievances [see 23/50], 1950-1967 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Lummus Co.: Grievances [see 23/50], 1950-1967 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Lummus Co.: Minutes: Membership meetings, meeting notices. 1958 letter from shop steward on internal disputes., 1956-1966 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Lummus Co.: Minutes: Membership meetings, meeting notices. 1958 letter from shop steward on internal disputes., 1956-1966 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Lummus Co.: Minutes: Membership meetings, meeting notices. 1958 letter from shop steward on internal disputes., 1956-1966 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence: New York and Newark branches, early problems with employees refusing to join union; company policies; discussions of work conditions, duties, layoffs, grievances; Honesdale PA plant information from IAM local (1954); correspondence relating to negotiations and strike., 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Lummus Co.: Correspondence [see 24/1], 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Lummus Co.: Circulars to members, wage increases (1951-1952), disputes with management, internal union dispute (1959), 1948-1962 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Lummus Co.: Benefit plans includes employees' statistical data and minutes of the committee. (Sampled forms), 1949-1963 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Lummus Co.: [See 24/21], 1949-1963 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Lummus Co.: [See 24/21], 1949-1963 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Lummus Co.: [See 24/21], 1949-1963 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Lummus Co.: [See 24/21], 1949-1963 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Lummus Co.: General data: company publications, description of their "design models," employees abroad, seniority lists, 1947-1969 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Lummus Co.: General data [see 24/26], 1947-1969 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Lummus Co.: General data [see 24/26], 1947-1969 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Lummus Co.: General data [see 24/26], 1947-1969 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Lummus Co.: General data [see 24/26], 1947-1969 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Lummus Co.: General data [see 24/26], 1947-1969 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Lummus Co.: General data [see 24/26], 1947-1969 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Lummus Co.: General data [see 24/26], 1947-1969 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Lummus Co.: General data [see 24/26], 1947-1969 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Lummus Co.: General data [see 24/26], 1947-1969 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Lummus Co.: General data [see 24/26], 1947-1969 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: Local 66 maintains unit when Lummuss Honesdale, Pa. plant is transferred to Yuba (1957). Lummus correspondence from 1954; Yuba contracts for 1958-1960 until layoff of unit when plant is moved to Tulsa, 1961. Grievances on layoffs indicate company's final strategy., 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Yuba Consolidated Industries: [See 24/37], 1954-1961 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): Representation includes original recognition and raid by Allied Trades Union, Local 18 [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1964, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/1], 1964, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/1], 1964, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/1], 1964, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/1], 1964, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/1], 1964, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/1], 1964, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): Contracts. See also Box 29 [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1953-1962 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): Negotiations: includes company work rules and data prior to first contract; 1955 strike; subsequent contracts. [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1954-1959 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/9], 1954-1959 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/9], 1954-1959 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/9], 1954-1959 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/9], 1954-1959 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): Labor-management conferences: handwritten notes [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1955-1958 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): Grievances and arbitration. See also Correspondence and Labor/Management Files. [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1956-1961 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/15], 1956-1961 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/15], 1956-1961 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/15], 1956-1961 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/15], 1956-1961 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/15], 1956-1961 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/15], 1956-1961 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/15], 1956-1961 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/15], 1956-1961 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): Employees meetings: minutes, notices, attendance lists [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1954-1960 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): Employees meetings: minutes, notices, attendance lists [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1954-1960 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): Correspondence: 1954-1958 sole woman member of negotiating committee resigns to avoid embarrassment; 1958 status of union/company relations; Holmes, international organizer on internal disputes [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1954-1961 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/26], 1954-1961 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/26], 1954-1961 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/26], 1954-1961 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/26], 1954-1961 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): [See 25/26], 1954-1961 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): Pension plans: correspondence and negotiations [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1955-1961 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): Pension plans: correspondence and negotiations [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1955-1961 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): Dues check-offs and seniority lists (sampled) [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1955-1961 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): Dues check-offs and seniority lists (sampled) [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1955-1961 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (first affiliation): Dues check-offs and seniority lists (sampled) [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1955-1961 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (after re-affiliation): Circulars to members [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1964-1968 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (after re-affiliation): Negotiations [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1965-1976 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (after re-affiliation): Negotiations [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1965-1976 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (after re-affiliation): Correspondence: 1964 fight to regain unit; 1965 strike by Local 66 incurs strained relations with the production workers UAW Local 365; 1964-1967 files include complaint about new automatic drafting machine and correspondence from prior union Local 18; 1968-1971, settling a physical confrontation between two members; impending layoffs. [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1964-1976 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (after re-affiliation): [See 25/40], 1964-1976 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (after re-affiliation): [See 25/40], 1964-1976 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (after re-affiliation): [See 25/40], 1964-1976 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (after re-affiliation): [See 25/40], 1964-1976 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (after re-affiliation): [See 25/40], 1964-1976 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (after re-affiliation): General data: seniority lists and pension plan [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1962-1965 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype (after re-affiliation): General data: seniority lists and pension plan [NOTE: Box 25 Missing], 1962-1965 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Port Authority: Representation (and the fight for recognition) - correspondence with notes, memos, clippings; issues include anti-union statements, organizing, meal allowances, "annual" employees, retirement plan and military credits, employee questionnaire, union officers, inflation and pay benefits. Other Representation materials have been placed in separate folders as follows., 1968-1976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/1], 1968-1976 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/1], 1968-1976 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/1], 1968-1976 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/1], 1968-1976 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/1], 1968-1976 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/1], 1968-1976 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Port Authority: Representation - composition of bargaining unit (M-C-S/managerial-confidential-supervisory: designation of "managerial" workers excluded from union). These records consist of earlier job classification sheets and internal PA hearings and correspondence. 1976-1978 materials for the PA Employment Relations Panel cases MCS 77-1 and 77-2: witness lists, organizational chart, job specifications and employee objections, related White Collar Report, BNA, 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/8], 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/8], 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/8], 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/8], 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/8], 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/8], 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/8], 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/8], 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/8], 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/8], 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/8], 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/8], 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/8], 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/8], 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Port Authority: Representation dues deductions. PA policy and problems in honoring the deduction requests (1970-1971), correspondence, routine forms and memos., 1969-1973 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/23], 1969-1973 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/23], 1969-1973 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Port Authority: Representation [see 26/23], 1969-1973 (Box 26, Folder 26)